{
    "subject": "resource/Otto_H\u00f6lder",
    "predicate": "property/doctoralAdvisor",
    "object": "resource/Paul_du_Bois-Reymond",
    "human_readable": "Otto H\u00f6lder's doctoral advisor was Paul du Bois-Reymond.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9506303071975708,
            "question": "Who was Otto H\u00f6lder's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9029356241226196,
            "question": "Was Paul du Bois-Reymond a professor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9000661969184875,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Otto H\u00f6lder and Paul du Bois-Reymond?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8374818563461304,
            "question": "What was Paul du Bois-Reymond known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7177640795707703,
            "question": "What are some key contributions made by Paul du Bois-Reymond?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6553653478622437,
            "question": "In what field did Otto H\u00f6lder specialize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4679853916168213,
            "question": "How did the work of Paul du Bois-Reymond influence later mathematicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35969802737236023,
            "question": "Did Otto H\u00f6lder have any notable students?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25613492727279663,
            "question": "Were there any significant mathematical advancements during Otto H\u00f6lder's time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.031061047688126564,
            "question": "Who were some other prominent mathematicians of that era?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Otto H\u00f6lder's doctoral advisor was Paul du Bois-Reymond.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3824_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant mathematical advancements during Otto H\u00f6lder's time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3824_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Otto H\u00f6lder have any notable students?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3824_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the work of Paul du Bois-Reymond influence later mathematicians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3824_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3824_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not indicate that Paul du Bois-Reymond was Otto H\u00f6lder's doctoral advisor. In fact, the information suggests that Otto H\u00f6lder was a student of Leopold Kronecker, Karl Weierstra\u00df, and Ernst Kummer at the Polytechnikum in Berlin."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Text mentions Otto H\u00f6lder was a student of Leopold Kronecker, Karl Weierstra\u00df, and Ernst Kummer.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Otto H\u00f6lder was supervised by Ernst Kummer.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Otto H\u00f6lder studied at the University of Stuttgart and Berlin, where his advisor was Leopold Kronecker, Karl Weierstra\u00df, and Ernst Kummer, not Paul du Bois-Reymond.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}